## Parjanya Modi

India



parjanyamodi@gmail.com



9737426927



linkedin.com/in/parjanyamodi



parjanyamodi.com

## Summary

Experienced Co-Owner with a demonstrated history of working in the industry. Skilled in Engineering, Network Security, Enterprise Network Security, Adobe Photoshop, and Security. Strong business development professional with an Ongoing Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Computer Science and Engineering from B. M. S. College of Engineering.

## **Experience**

#### Technoler Founder

**Techalier** 

Feb 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

## Web Development Intern

Bullspree

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 (3 months)

## IT Support Technician

Bullspree

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 (3 months)

## Is Internshala Student Partner

Internshala

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021 (4 months)

#### **Education**



B. M. S. College of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science and Engineering 2019 - 2023

## Shree C C Shah Sarvajanik English Medium High School

High School Diploma, Science 2007 - 2019

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Technical Support Fundamentals - Coursera

Computer Networks Security Technologies and Tools for Network Admins and Cyber Security Officers - Udemy

U-aa588512-431e-4f41-8fbe-487e3a8ab455

- Engineering: Undergraduate & Masters Asia Virtual Experience Program InsideSherpa
  e2HZcoRgQugtitgLW
- NSE 1 Network Security Associate Fortinet Issued Apr 2020 Expires Apr 2022
  XhX4jEwAgP
- NSE 2 Network Security Associate Fortinet Issued Apr 2020 Expires Apr 2022
  NzQx0vSSGI
- The Evolution of Cybersecurity Fortinet
- The Threat Landscape Fortinet
- (A) Technology Consulting Virtual Internship InsideSherpa CZCoW2quKwNAmey5T
- Cyber Security Global Virtual Internship InsideSherpa CNMap5Bn8En5TL5pJ
- Basics of Database Design & Development Udemy UC-dfadb129-075e-408e-8f61-3478acd9bc82
- Intel® Network Academy Network Transformation 102 Coursera 55W2UVJSF2X8
- Certified Ethical Hacking & Cyber Security: Beginner To Pro Udemy UC-330a8a3e-1a1b-4430-8311-1fbda17119d3
- CSFPC™ CertiProf
  Issued Apr 2021 Expires Apr 2023
  61831596

### RWVCPC™ Professional Certificate - CertiProf

Issued Apr 2021 - Expires Apr 2023 61848631

# Cyber Security Foundation Professional Certificate - CSFPC™ - CertiProf Issued Apr 2021 - Expires Apr 2023

Remote Work and Virtual Collaboration Professional Certificate - RWVCPC - CertiProf
Issued Apr 2021 - Expires Apr 2023

#### **Skills**

Network Security • Enterprise Network Security • Network Security Expert • Hardware • Security • Engineering • Adobe Photoshop • Technical Support • IT Hardware Support • Computer Hardware